delphiforums.com 2003-06-21

# Delphi Forums: Privacy Policy

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to Delphi Forums. Because we ask for some basic personal information during registration, we want you to be fully informed of how this information is gathered and used. 

  1. REGISTRATION
  2. INFORMATION DELPHI FORUMS REQUESTS
  3. CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT
  4. PARTICIPATION
  5. COOKIES
  6. DELPHI & NON-DELPHI FORUMS
  7. COOKIES
  8. PUBLIC FORUMS
  9. SECURITY
  10. TERMINATION
  11. SUMMARY

**Registration**  
Some basic personal information is required in order to register with Delphi Forums: 

  * **Name** \- Your first and last name help us to personalize your online experience. For example, your "My Forums" list of favorite online communities may feature your first and/or last name. 
  * **Email Address** \- By providing your email address, you can receive important messages via your existing email account. Message board notifications, personalized My Forums newsletters, and messages sent to you by other Delphi Forums members rely on the email address you provide when you register. 
  * **User Name** \- This is how you are identified when you participate in forums. While many other aspects of your account can be updated regularly, your user name cannot be changed.

 -top-  
  
**Information Delphi Forums Requests**  
When you register, you are asked to give demographic information (like birth year, occupation, and gender). We ask you to tell us a little about yourself so we can better understand the types of people who register. This information can also be used to provide you with content that may be of interest to you, and to show you advertisements that are relevant to your demographic information. Delphi Forums uses outside ad companies to display ads on its sites. These ads may contain cookies. While Delphi Forums uses cookies in other parts of its sites, the ad companies also use cookies with the ads displayed, and Delphi Forums may not have access to this information. 

 -top-  
  
**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**  
Any data—except email address—that Delphi Forums collects on children under 13 years of age will be discarded in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Email addresses of children under 13 submitted during registration are kept by Delphi Forums for identification purposes only, and under no circumstances are displayed or made publicly available. 

 -top-  
  
**Participation**  
The above describes information that is provided "actively" - meaning, you choose to submit this information to us when you join Delphi Forums, or update your account at any point after having joined. Some other information is provided "passively" - meaning, that Delphi Forums obtains this information when you login to your Delphi account and use the service. This is done primarily through the use of "cookies." Cookies are used on Delphi Forums to verify your login information, and to optionally store your password in your browser so that you do not need to type it in each time you visit. Any time that you point your browser to a 'members-only' area, Delphi Forums checks your browser's cookie file to see if you have already logged in, and if you have, you're taken right to the page that you have requested. If not, you'll be directed to the Delphi Forums login screen, where you can quickly and easily login to your account, or signup for Delphi Forums if you are not yet a member. Cookies are also used in conjunction with some ad banners to determine their effectiveness. 

 -top-  
  
**Cookies**  
  
Delphi Forums uses cookies to customize your experience while using the Forums. A cookie is a small text file that many Web sites write through your browser when you visit them. A cookie can only be read by the site that places it, so Delphi Forums can't "see where you've been" based on any other cookies in your browser. Cookies are generally supported in version 3.0 and newer of Internet Explorer, 2.02 and newer of Netscape, and 3.0 and newer of AOL. Netscape Navigator uses a single file called "cookies.txt" to record all cookies, and you can open this file in any text editor to see what it looks like. On a Macintosh computer, the Netscape cookie file is called "MagicCookie". Internet Explorer uses a separate file for each cookie, which typically reside in "C:\Windows\Profiles\User\Cookies." Most browsers also allow the option of displaying a warning before accepting a cookie, or refusing all cookies. Declining cookies while participating in forums may result in some of features not working properly. 

Delphi Forums uses 24/7 Media and other third-party advertising companies to serve the ads that you see on our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by third party advertising companies, go to [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). To learn more about 24/7 Media, including your ability to opt out of 24/7 Media system go to <http://www.247media.com/privacy>. 

 -top-  
  
**Delphi & Non-Delphi Forums **  
  
Delphi Forums, along with many other companies, relies on Prospero Technologies to host our online communities and related data. Participation in a given company's forums includes the sharing of some of your personal information with both Prospero and the company that operates the forum. You will be warned before your information is shared with another company, and will have the opportunity to decline if desired. Any company with which your information is shared will have it's own privacy policy. 

As a registered user, you may receive email messages on a regular basis to keep you apprised of your membership status and inform you of new services available to you. Examples of this include the personalized 'My Forums' email, which shows you an overview of activity in your favorite online communities. If you create your own online community, we will also email you traffic summary reports for your own forum on a regular basis. Included in each of these messages are simple instructions on how to remove yourself from these mailings if you do not wish to receive them in the future. 

 -top-  
  
**Public Forums**  
Delphi Forums hosts message boards, chat and other services for both public and private forums. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in public forums becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

 -top-  
  
**Security**  
Delphi Forums' site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control. Delphi Forums' servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about its users. 

 -top-  
  
**Termination**  
You can elect to terminate your membership with Delphi Forums at any time. Simply go to your [My Forums](http://myforums.com/) page, scroll down to the "My Info" menu on the left-hand side of the page, and select the "My Preferences" link. On the "My Preferences" page and scroll down to the "Account Status" section. Check the box next to "Want to cancel your account?" and scroll down to the bottom of the page to the "Submit" button. Click on the "Submit" button to cancel your account. Upon termination, your account information will _not_ necessarily be removed entirely from Delphi Forums - this is to reserve your identity so that no one else can create a new account with your membername or email address, and also allows you the privilege of reactivating your account at a later date if you wish to use Delphi Forums again. The termination of your Delphi Forums membership will not automatically terminate any affiliated memberships or registrations you have formed through Delphi Forums. If, after having joined a Delphi partner's service, you wish to be removed, you should contact that service directly to have your membership terminated. 

 -top-  
  
**Summary**  
In this electronic era, when personal information can easily be obtained through various sources, Delphi appreciates the sensitivity of any private information that you disclose to us. It is our intention to treat your account information with the highest level of care. 

 -top-
